instagantt.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy

This Privacy Policy covers the information we collect about you when you use our product. Instagantt refers to 5Rabbits LLC. We refer to our product as "the service".

This privacy policy takes effect on May 25, 2018. This changes have been made in order to be compliant with the GDPR.

Previous version of our privacy policy can be found here.

###  Information we collect from you 

We collect information associated to your personal data (Name, E-Mail address, Public Photo, and any other attribute you would like to provide us), when you create or modify an account. This information is used to provide you the service. We may share this information with our data processors (our database provider, G Suite, or our servers provider, for example), which are third party companies we use to provide you the service. 

We collect information associated to your Content, which includes Projects, tasks, descriptions, dates, and all other content you may post to the service when using our product, or content you may fetch from a connection to ther third party service like Asana.

We collect and store your Content when you create a Public Snapshot (public read only link you can share in the web for access with read only privileges, without a secured account). It's created under your consent to be accessible through a public link.

We collect information you provide us through our Support Channels.

We collect information associated to your Payment details, like billing address, billing name, billing e-mail. Other secure information like credit cards is collected and processed by our Secure Payments Processor partner, where we don't have direct access to sensitive data like Credit Card Numbers.

We and our partner services use Cookies and other tracking technologies to identify you across our service, and enable access to the products or our third party products (our Support Channel, or our Internal Analytics platform, for example). We may store data regarding to your device (model, screen size, operative system, and many other device-related attributes) as well as IP address and other network-related attributes.

### Information we collect from other sources

Other users may provide information about you when someone invites you to share a Workbook, for example.

We receive and collect information from other services when you link them with Instagantt. For example, if you log into Instagantt using your Google Account, we receive your name, email address and public photo.

### How we use your information

We use the information for different purposes and in many ways, including: 

  * Provide, operate, and maintain our Services;
  * Improve, personalize, and expand our Services and your Experience;
  * Understand and analyze how you use our Service;
  * Develop new features, services, and functionality;
  * Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the Service, and for marketing and promotional purposes;
  * Process your transactions;
  * Send you text messages and push notifications;
  * Find and prevent fraud; and
  * For compliance purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service, or other legal rights, or as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency.

### How we share your information

As a collaboration tool, we may share information with certain third parties in order to provide the service. We share information we collect about you in the ways discussed below, but we are not in the business of selling information about you to advertisers or other third parties.

  * Sharing with other Instagantt users
  * When you use the service, we share certain information about you with other Service users (for example, when you invite colleagues to collaborate on a workbook with you).
  * For collaboration: You can create content, which may contain information about you, and grant permission to others to see, share, edit, copy and download that content. Please be aware that some features of the services like Public Snapshots are publicly available, meaning any content posted, including information about you, can be publicly viewed and indexed by and returned in search results of search engines.

Sharing with third parties 

  * We share information with third parties that help us operate, provide, improve, integrate, customize, support and market our Services.
  * Service Providers: We work with third-party service providers to provide website and application development, hosting, maintenance, backup, storage, virtual infrastructure, payment processing, analysis and other services for us, which may require them to access or use information about you. If a service provider needs to access information about you to perform services on our behalf, they do so under close instruction from us, including policies and procedures designed to protect your information.
  * Third-Party Widgets: Some of our Services contain widgets and social media features, such as the Twitter "tweet" button. These widgets and features collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the Services, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Widgets and social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 
  * With your consent: We share information about you with third parties when you give us consent to do so. For example, we often display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our public websites. With your consent, we may post your name alongside the testimonial. 
  * Compliance with Enforcement Requests and Applicable Laws; Enforcement of Our Rights: In exceptional circumstances, we may share information about you with a third party if we believe that sharing is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, including to meet national security requirements, (b) enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service, (c) protect the security or integrity of our products and services, (d) protect Atlassian, our customers or the public from harm or illegal activities, or (e) respond to an emergency which we believe in good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person. For more information on how we respond to government requests, see our Guidelines for Law Enforcement and our Transparency Report. 

### Your Content

While using Instagantt Standalone (without Asana), you can create Gantt Charts, comments, notes, and other content you'd like to post to the service when available, handled and stored in our own infrastructure. This content may be shared by you with other users of the service, like inviting collaborators to a Project or Workbook. We may use third party companies (sub processors) to provide you the service. 

While using Instagantt for Asana, the service allows you to view the content of your Asana Account in the way of a Gantt Chart, and also gives you the ability to create and edit content from it. All your content is ruled by Asana’s Terms of Service, and the service will never access your content without your permission.

### Access to Your Content

You are granting Instagantt to access your content and your Asana content (when you're using Instagantt for Asana) for the following purposes: i) fill the content inside the Instagantt Application, ii) Make modifications whenever you request the Instagantt Application to do so. Instagantt will never access your content without your knowledge for a purpose different than the intended in providing the service. All read/write operations to Asana API or to the Standalone version are triggered by the user, using our web interface or our API.

### Legal bases for processing (for EEA users):

If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws. We collect and use your information only where: 

  * We need it to provide you the Services, including to operate the Services, provide customer support and personalized features;
  * You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose; or 
  * We need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place. Where we are using your information because we or a third party (e.g. your employer) have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Services. 

Also, you're under the following rights:

  * If you wish to request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by emailing hello@instagantt.com.
  * If you wish to object the processing of your personal information, you can do so at any time by emailing hello@instagantt.com.
  * If you wish to request portability of your personal information, you can do so at any time by emailing hello@instagantt.com.
  * Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

### Children's privacy

We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13, and children under 13 are prohibited from using the service. If you learn that a child has provided us with personal information in violation of this Privacy Policy, you can alert us at hello@instagantt.com. 

### Security

We will use industry standard technical and organizational security measures in connection with the storage, processing and transfer of your Content that are designed to protect the integrity of that Content and to guard against unauthorized or unlawful access to, use of, or processing of such Content. Instagantt does not save any information about project tasks when using it in connection with Asana. All the information is fetched and pushed directly from and to the Asana API. If you decide to create a Baseline or a Public Snapshot (shareable), this information will be stored on our own resources. When using Instagantt Standalone, all data created is managed and stored in our own infrastructure, secured by industry level standards.

### Data Retention

We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax, or accounting requirements).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

### Personal Data

Instagantt will never sell your personal data for any purpose. We're not on the business of selling personal data to advertisers or any interedted party. 

### Termination

You are free to stop using our Service at any time. We also reserve the right to suspend or end the Service at any time at our discretion and without notice. We may also terminate or suspend your access to the Service at any time if you are not complying with these Terms or if you are using the Service in a manner that we believe may cause us financial or legal liability.

### Modifications to the Service

The Service may be modified from time to time, often without prior notice to you. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your acceptance of such modifications. If you are not satisfied with a modification we make to the Service, your sole remedy is to terminate your use of the Service.

### No Warranty

THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. INSTAGANTT IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY THIRD PARTY CONTENT THAT YOU DOWNLOAD OR OTHERWISE OBTAIN THROUGH THE USE OF THE SERVICE OR FOR ANY DAMAGE OR LOSS OF DATA THAT MAY RESULT.

### International Data Transfer

In connection with providing you the Service Instagantt may transfer, store and process your Content in the U.S. or in any other country in which Instagantt or its agents maintain facilities. By using the Service you consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your Content.
